egscans.com 2018-03-04

# Privacy Policy :: EGScans

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Easy Going Scans collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the egscans.com website and all sub-domains ("Egscans.com"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Easy Going Scans.

### Personally Identifiable Information (PII)

Egscans.com may collect Personally Identifiable Information (PII) from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name and email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect PII from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply PII, accepting that certain Site related activities will not be made available to them.

### Sharing your personal information

Easy Going Scans will never sell, trade or otherwise disclose User PII to third parties. We take your private information seriously.

Generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any PII regarding visitors and Users may be shared with trusted affiliates, such as wordpress.com and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with Egscans.com. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to Egscans.com, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Egscans.com uses "cookies" to enhance User experience. The User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about website usage. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If so, note that some parts of Egscans.com may not function properly.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

### How we use collected information

Easy Going Scans may collect and use Users’ PII for the following purposes:

  *  **To improve customer service**  
Information you provide helps us respond to User customer service requests and support User needs more efficiently.
  *  **To improve Egscans.com**  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  *  **To send periodic emails**  
Easy Going Scans may use User email addresses to respond to inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Our Site is in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

Sensitive and private data exchange between Egscans.com and its Users happens over an SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on Egscans.com that link to the sites and services of our partners, advertisers, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from Egscans.com. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to Egscans.com, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

### Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Changes to this privacy policy

Easy Going Scans reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes and stay informed regarding the ways Easy Going Scans helps to protect any PII we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using Egscans.com, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use Egscans.com. Your continued use of Egscans.com following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

The Easy Going Scans Privacy Policy was last modified on February 10th, 2013.
